Guide to the Michael Johnson Papers, 1881-1995 05656
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
Michael Johnson papers
1881-1995
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
05656
26.75 Linear Feet (25 containers)
Michael Johnson worked as an organizer for the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union ( ILGWU) (1934-1955), becoming a labor education director (1955-1965), before joining the Pennsylvania AFL-CIO and the Pennsylvania Public Utilities Commission.
Access Restrictions
For information on accessing this collection please contact the Special Collections Research Services Unit at ul-spcolref@lists.psu.edu.
Biographical or Historical Note
Michael Johnson was born Michael Sussman in New York on 10 May 1912. Soon thereafter his family moved to Detroit, but around 1922 they returned to New York. While in high school he took the nom de plume Michael Johnson, and later he made that his legal name. After graduating from high school at the age of 16, he studied at Columbia University, but lack of money obliged him to drop out and take a job in Harlem as a presser in a coat factory, where he organized workers and a strike. In 1932 he married Sulamith Cohen; they had two daughters. For two decades, 1934 to 1955, Johnson worked an organizer, a district manager, and a director for the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) in the northeastern region of Pennsylvania. He was education director for the Pennsylvania Federation of Labor (1955-1960) and then returned to the ILGWU as its education director (1960-1965). Johnson served as executive vice president of the Pennsylvania AFL-CIO (1965-1975) and then finished his career as a member of the Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission (1975-1985), where he was renowned as a fiery advocate of consumer rights. He died in Philadelphia on 17 October 1995.
Collection Overview
The bulk of the Michael Johnson Papers documents his service on the Pennsylvania Public Utilities Commission from 1975 to 1985. There are also papers from his term as executive vice president of the Pennsylvania AFL-CIO from 1965 to 1975, and biographical materials, photographs, and a musical composed by Johnson for the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (1950).
- Biographical Material, 01
  - American Assembly report, 1964 (Box 1)
  - Big Run calendar, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Biographical information, 1960-1962 (Box 1)
  - Biographical sketch, 1976-1985 (Box 1)
  - Birthday cards, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Brandywine Conservancy, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Cards, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Cards, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Christmas cards, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Clout of Mike Johsnon (Discover magazine), June 2, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Committee and Activists/table seating, undated (Box 1)
  - Community Services Counselling Classes instructor certificate, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Condolences, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Contracts/Receipts/Correspondence, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Finances, undated (Box 1)
  - From the New Frontier to the New Revolution, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Fineman, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Letters-honoring, 1981-1985 (Box 1)
  - Maverick PUC Leader Fights Hikes (from The Sentinal), September 24, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Mellon's Millions, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Memorial contributions to various charities, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Memorial Fund plaque, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - New York Times Magazine, April 25, 1982 (Box 21)
  - New York Times Magazine, May 2, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Obituary, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Personal, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Personal, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
  - Personal, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Personal, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Personal, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Personal-Allentown conference photograph, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Personal-Allentown conference photograph, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Personal and general information, 1980-1985 (Box 1)
  - Personal - correspondence, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Personal-Miriam Pritchon resume, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Personal-name change, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Personal-telegrams, 1944-1958 (Box 1)
  - Philadelphia Business Journal, December 31, 1984 - January 6, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Remarks by M. Johnson (at the Histadrut Dinner), March 26, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Resume-Johnson, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 1)
  - Social Security card application, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Sympathy-correspondence, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Telephone numbers-P.F.U.U., undated (Box 1)
  - Tragedy at Bridesburg - 54 Who Died (Philadelphia Inquirer), October 26, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Twelve Days of Christmas, 1973 (Box 1)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 02
  - A View from Both Sides by Yevette Richards, undated (Box 2)
  - Allentown Local III photograph, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Arrangements committee, undated (Box 2)
  - As I sit and ponder, The time has come, photograph, undated (Box 2)
  - Business agent's wife, undated (Box 2)
  - Garment workers gather, Tzena, Tzena, Tzena, undated (Box 2)
  - G.E.B. discussion-photograph, 1953 (Box 2)
  - I want to be a person, undated (Box 2)
  - ILGWU local 108 booklet, 1953 (Box 1)
  - It's time, undated (Box 2)
  - My name is Mary Brown, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
  - My name is Mary Brown, 1950-1952 (Box 2)
  - Northeast Department Report, 1950 (Box 2)
  - Only together, undated (Box 2)
  - Organizing, undated (Box 2)
  - Pantomine, arranger,slides, photograph, undated (Box 2)
  - Proposed changes to musical, undated (Box 2)
  - Shop chairman Joe, At the ILG Health Center, undated (Box 2)
  - Springfield conference script, 1951 (Box 2)
  - Story of Mary Brown, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Strong statement opposing Senate Bill 596, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Telephone numbers-P.F.U.U., undated (Box 2)
  - That's what a good girl should do, undated (Box 2)
  - The one and only one--it's D.D., undated (Box 2)
  - Those were the good old days, undated (Box 2)
  - Three Intellectual giants-"It's time"-telegram, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Three Intellectual giants-Morrison Hotel, undated (Box 2)
  - Tomorrow (Manana), undated (Box 2)
  - Union Advisory Committee of the Pennsylvania State University, 1954 (Box 2)
  - Union Health Center, undated (Box 2)
  - Union label, 1960-1963 (Box 2)
  - Union makes it so, and other verse, undated (Box 2)
  - We're on our way to the convention, undated (Box 2)
  - You've got that something, We greet you, Oh, ye who have battled, 1944 (Box 1)
- Pennsylvania American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 03
  - Administrative code of 1929 amendment-H.B. 175, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - AFL-CIO News, 1965-1971 (Box 3)
  - AFL-CIO News, 1982 (Box 3)
  - AFL-CIO News, 1983 (Box 4)
  - AFL-CIO News Service, 1965 (Box 3)
  - AI Labor Letter, 1979 (Box 3)
  - AI Labor Letter, 1983 (Box 4)
  - AI Labor Letter, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Allentown Local III-photograph, 1964 (Box 2)
  - American Federationist, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - American Income Life Insurance Co., 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - American Income Life Insurance Company, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Berger for Congress, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Block, Harry, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Block, Harry letter, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Boyer's labor statements, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Campaign for Governor, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Campaigns-Shapp-Wambaugh, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Campaigns-Shapp-Wambaugh, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Center... Democratic Institutions reports, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Constitution of PA-AFL-CIO, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Constitutional convention, 8th, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Constitutional Convention, 24th Annual, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Constitutional Convention, 25th annual, 1984 (Box 4)
  - COPE, 1965 (Box 2)
  - COPE, 1967 (Box 3)
  - COPE, 1968 (Box 3)
  - COPE-Critical Path method, 1974 (Box 3)
  - COPE dinner-Lehigh County Labor Council, 1979 (Box 3)
  - COPE-statistical information, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Department of Labor and Industry-accomplishments, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
  - Developments in the consumer credit area..., 1968 (Box 3)
  - Directory, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Economic plan and review, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Energy Transportation Security Act, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Executive vice-president election, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Executive vice-president election-photograph, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Finance Facts article, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Ford Agency report, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Histadrut, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Histadrut-testimonial dinner, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Howard agency report, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Humphrey, Hubert, 1967 (Box 3)
  - In Public Service, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Insurance, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Job Corps, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Johnson and others-union functions, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Johnson speaking appearances-union information, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Labor Chronicle, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Labor Day appearance, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Labor Dinner Dance, 2nd Annual (Hershey, PA) - 12x16 poster, August 30,1975 (Box 25)
  - Labor dinner dance-honor, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Labor Heritage Songbook, 1983-1990 (Box 4)
  - Labor Letter, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Legislative bills, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Legislative directory, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - Legislative directory-federal and state, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Legislative related, 1955-1963 (Box 2)
  - Legislative-related materials, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
  - Letters, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Lists-affiliated and unaffiliated persons, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Lobbying registration, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Manpower, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Manual of Corporate Investigations, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Martyrs, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Meany's statements, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Michener, James picnic-photographs, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Minimum wage, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Minsker Progressive Branch 99, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Morand, Martin, 1963 (Box 2)
  - Morand, Martin, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Name lists, undated (Box 4)
  - News AFL-CIO press release, 1983 (Box 4)
  - News clippings, 1985 (Box 4)
  - News from the AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Newsletters,magazines, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Newsletter-magazines, 1976-1982 (Box 3)
  - Newsletters,magazines, 1979-1985 (Box 3)
  - Newspaper and magazine articles, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Newspaper articles-PAC monies, 1979 (Box 3)
  - North Annual Institute-UNESCO brochure, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
  - Object III report, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - O'Donoghue testimonial dinner, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Organizations affiliated with AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 3)
  - PA AFL-CIO communications, 1983 (Box 4)
  - PA AFL-CIO Institute application, 1983 (Box 4)
  - PA AFL-CIO News, 1962-1975 (Box 2)
  - PA. AFL-CIO Newsletter, 1975 (Box 25)
  - PA General Fund Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - PA Goods and Services... Act redraft, 1968 (Box 3)
  - PA House Bill 7 and Senate Bill 10, 1966 (Box 3)
  - PA labor councils, undated (Box 4)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO News, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Pennsylvania AFL-CIO News, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Pennsylvania Building and Construction Trades Council letters, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Pennsylvania Federationist, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Pennsylvania Labor newsletter, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Pennsylvania Legislative Directory, 1983-1984 (Box 25)
  - Pennsylvania Public Interest Coalition, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Philadelphia Council AFL-CIO Minutes, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Photographs, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Plant totals, undated (Box 4)
  - Registration, Election and Voting Age Population Statistics, 1960-1966 (Box 25)
  - Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
  - Resignations-Johnson, Lovell, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Right to work, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Right to work, Group Research news, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Sisterhood and Solidarity flyer, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Social Security, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Solidarity Day III, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Speech, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Study of the mayoralty race in Pittsburgh, PA, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Study of the political climate, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Tax material, 1963-1970 (Box 2)
  - Third constitutional convention officers' report, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Time study institute, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Unemployment insurance, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Union sponsored scholarships, 1983 (Box 4)
  - U.S. elections, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Wall Street Journal articles, August 24, 25, 27, 1965 (Box 3)
  - Work without compensation, right to treatment, 1967-1971 (Box 3)
  - Workers' Compensation, undated (Box 4)
- Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission, 04
  - Ability to pay hearing, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Access charges, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Act creating three commissions, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Acts, 1963-1978 (Box 4)
  - Address of the Honorable Dick Thornburgh, Governor, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Addresses, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Administrative judge issues, 1978 (Box 6)
  - A Look Inside- I Guide to PUC, 1985 (Box 16)
  - A Look Inside-II Consumers and the PUC, 1985 (Box 16)
  - A Look Inside-III Rate Case Comparison, 1985 (Box 16)
  - American Water Works service Co., Inc., 1983 (Box 10)
  - Amicus curiae brief of Michael Johnson, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Amicus curiae brief of Michael Johnson in definitive form, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Annual reports-elections, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Appeals, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Arctic Gas project, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Barasch v. PA PUC, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Barasch v. PUC-Motion to suppress brief, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Bath County pumped storage project, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Bell, Clarence speech, November 27, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Bell Telephone petition for partial waiver, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Benefits and cost of load management, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Big Run, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Big Run Free Militia presentation speech, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Brief for Commerical Complainants, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Brown Manor Water Company position statement, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Bureaus-information received, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Bureaus-memos/information, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Bureaus-memos/information from, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Bureaus- memos/information from, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Bureaus-memos/information from, January - August, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Bureaus-memos/information, September - December 1983 (Box 11)
  - Button, New Yorker, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Cable television act H.B. 2323, 1973-1978 (Box 4)
  - Cable TV, 1979 (Box 8)
  - California Public Utilities Comm. (Cash Allowances), October 4, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Canada-U.S. Trade in Natural Gas, Edge, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Case Activity Spreadsheets, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Cash working capital MJ, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
  - Certificates of necessity-Senate Bill 1032, 1979 (Box 8)
  - City of Pittsburgh v. Pennsylvania PUC, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Clarence Bell support, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Commission jurisdiction municipal corporations H.B. 1960, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
  - Commonwealth of PA before Environmental Hearing Board, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Commonwealth Printing Act 455, 1961 (Box 4)
  - Company publications, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Comparison Cost of Electriciry between companies in PA, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Conclusion of Services policy SP-616, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Concurring Opinion of M. Johnson (Emergency Surcharge Petition by West Penn Power Co.), April 30, 1980 (Box 24)
  - Conference on Democratic Party Organization and Policy proceedings, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Congratulatory letters and response, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Connellsville et al. v. Western Pennsylvania Water Company, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - Construction work in progress S.B. 1366, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
  - Consumer Affairs Committee hearings, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Consumer Bill of Rights, 1977-1979 (Box 6)
  - Consumer Education proposal-Avinger, undated (Box 6)
  - Consumer survey-Catherine Sprague, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence La Verne file, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Correspondence-LaVerne file, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Cost plus pricing meeting, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Deregulation of motor carriers... - Virginia, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Dissent of M. Johnson - (Philadelphia Electric Company), June 30, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Dissenting Opinion of M. Johnson - (Equitable Gas Comp.), undated (Box 24)
  - Dissenting Opinion of M. Johnson - (Philadelphia Electric Comp.), 1984 (Box 24)
  - Dissenting Opinons by M. Johnson on various cases, 1984 (Box 24)
  - Docket sheets filed-Columbia Gas, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-Duquesne, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-Equitable Gas, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-Keystone Water, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-North Penn Run Gas, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-Penn Power, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-PG&W, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-People's Gas, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-Philadelphia Electric, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-Philadelphia Sub. Water, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-PP&L, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Docket sheets filed-UGI Gas, 1981-1984 (Box 8)
  - Docket sheets filed-West Penn Water, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Dockets filed-Met. Ed., 1984 (Box 14)
  - Duquesne Light company, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Economic Recovery Act, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Election article materials-statements, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Electric Power Supply and Demand, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Electric utilities-report and brochure, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Electrical Utility Annual Summary Report appendix A, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Electirical utility management audit program and measurement criteria, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Employment policy statement-Goode, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Endorsements, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Energy assistance programs, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Energy companies, 1982-1985 (Box 9)
  - Energy Mobilization Board, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Energy publications, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Exceptions... To the recommended decision..., February 20, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Expenses, 1983-1985 (Box 11)
  - Financial reports-general public utilities, 1985 (Box 16)
  - First Class City Permanent Registration Act amendments, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Fixed utility rate filings, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Fluid bed technology, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Fortnightly, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Fortnightly, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Fortnightly, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Fuel adjustment clause, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Fuel adjustment clauses, 1982 (Box 9)
  - GAI reports-Chester site-Fossil Unit Cost study, 1984 (Box 14)
  - GAI reports-Generic Eastern site-Fossil Unit Cost study, 1984 (Box 14)
  - GAI reports-Limerick.. .Coal conversion study, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Gas cost rate-General Assembly letter, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Gas Daily, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Gas service lines and meter locations, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - Gas utility management audit program and measurement criteria, 1977 (Box 6)
  - General Assembly of PA bills, 1985 (Box 16)
  - General Public Utilities Corporation reports, 1984 (Box 14)
  - General rate cases, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Generic Access Charge proceeding, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Goadby v. PA PUC, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Guest et al. v. Blue Cross of Greater Philadelphia et al., 1976 (Box 5)
  - Hearing calendar, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Heating Problem, Osward, Sandusky, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Hero Corporation statements, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Home heating needs of low income households in Philadelphia, 1984 (Box 14)
  - House Bill 434 amendments, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Hubert Humphre Institute of Public Affairs, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Index-names-addresses-telephone, 1984 (Box 14)
  - INPO's evlaution of TMI's Unit I, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs-Memos/information from, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Intergovernmental affairs-memos/information, January - December, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs-Memos/Information, January - December, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Intergovernmental affairs-memos/information from, 1985 (Box 16)
  - International Gas Research Conference report, January - December, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Interstate access charges-Public input hearing, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Investment tax credit, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Invoices, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Joseph Horne Co. v. Pa PUC, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Joseph Horne Co. v. PA PUC, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Kovich, Allen, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Kukovich, Allen, undated (Box 25)
  - Legislative activity for 1983-1984 relevant to PUC, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Legislative director, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Letter from PA. Senator Clarence Bell to Phyllis Zitzer, November 8, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Letter from PA State Rep. William Lloyd Jr. to Linda Taliaferro, August 5, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Letter of Protest by Samuel Kirschman (Sale of Suburbin Lines), undated (Box 25)
  - Letter to House re H.B. 132, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Letter to Rep. George Hasay, March 11, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Letter to the Chair of the PA PUC, from the office of the Mayor of Philadelphia, November 27, 1985 (Box 24)
  - Letter to the PA. Senate and House, August 9, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Letters to the editor, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Lifeline electric rates... low-income ratepayers, vol. 1-3, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Lifeline rates legislation, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - Limerick generating station deferral, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Limerick II generating Station investigation-Rodberg testimony, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Limerick II.. .investigation hearings, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Limerick II report, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Limerick II-Select Committee Report, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Limerick nuclear generating station investigation, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Limerick Unit 2... Investigation recommended decision, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Limerock completion deferral motion, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Lobbyist issue, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Low income energy assistance program and budget, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Lukens Steel Co. v. PA PUC, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Mail, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Mail, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Mail, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Mail, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Mail, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Mail, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Mail, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Mail, April - July, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Mail-important, March - April, 1983 (Box 11)
  - Mail, January - March (Box 11)
  - Mail log, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Mail log-bureau memos, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Mail log-first class, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Mail, September - December, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Management summary-utility management audit programs, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Memos/Information from chairman and commissioners, March 1983 (Box 13)
  - Memos/information from chairman and commissioners, 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - Meter reading discharged, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Metro Transportation Company, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Metropolitan Edison Company, et al.-Three Mile Island, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Metropolitan Edison Company report, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Mid-Atlantic Regulatory Commission-executive committee statement, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Milestones Philadelphia electric Company, 1881-1981 (Box 9)
  - Motions, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Motions, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Motions, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Motions by commissioners, 1982 (Box 9)
  - NARUC, 1985 (Box 16)
  - NARUC Annal Regulatory Studies Program, 1977 (Box 6)
  - NARUC committee on gas minutes, 1985 (Box 16)
  - NARUC-Gas research institute update, 1985 (Box 16)
  - NARUC-letters/information, 1983 (Box 13)
  - National Association of Regulatory Utility Commissioners (NARUC), 1984 (Box 15)
  - National Energy Act Bill statement, 1977 (Box 6)
  - New Directions for Canadian-U.S. Energy Relations, 1985 (Box 16)
  - New Republic, 1982 (Box 10)
  - News clippings, 1974 (Box 4)
  - News clippings, 1977 (Box 6)
  - News clippings, 1978 (Box 7)
  - News clippings, 1979 (Box 8)
  - News clipping, 1981 (Box 9)
  - News clippings, 1982 (Box 10)
  - News clippings, 1983 (Box 13)
  - News clippings, 1984 (Box 15)
  - News clippings, 1985 (Box 16)
  - News clippings-departure, 1985 (Box 16)
  - News clippings re: PUC nomination, 1975 (Box 5)
  - News clippings re: PUC nomination-swearing-in, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Newsletter, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 16)
  - New York Times, May 13, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Nomination and election as commissioner, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Nomination hearing, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Office of Consumer Advocate, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Office of Consumer Advocate Annual Report, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Ohio Public Utilities Commission, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Opinion-PEC v. PUC, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Opinions, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Opinions, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Opinions, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Opinions, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Opinions, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Opinions, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Opinions, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Opinions, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Opinions-Commisssion rate case precedent and policies, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Opinion and order-Limerick 2 investigation, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Opinions-PA Supreme Court, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Order, 1980 (Box 8)
  - PA PUC v. Columbia Gas of PA, 1985 (Box 16)